<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WSJF Task Scheduler</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="header_title">WSJF Task Scheduler</string>
    <string name="header_subtitle">Version 1.0</string>

    <string name="pref_values_scale">Values Scale</string>
    <string name="pref_values_summ">Set the scale values of the jobs.</string>
    <string name="pref_scale_key" translatable="false">scale</string>
    <string name="pref_scale_default" translatable="false">10</string>

    <string name="details_job_title">Job Title</string>

    <string name="details_details">Details</string>
    <string name="details_job_title_hint">Title</string>
    <string name="details_job_description">Description</string>
    <string name="details_job_description_hint">Add Description</string>
    <string name="details_job_date">Date</string>
    <string name="details_job_time">Time</string>

    <string name="details_values">Values</string>
    <string name="details_user_value">User/Business Value</string>
    <string name="details_time_value">Time Value</string>
    <string name="details_rroe_value">Risk Reduction Value</string>
    <string name="details_job_size">Job Size Value</string>
    <string name="details_default_value">0</string>

    <string name="about_wsjf_title">WSJF</string>
    <string name="about_cod_title">Cost of Delay</string>
    <string name="about_job_duration_title">Job Duration</string>
    <string name="about_result_title">Result</string>
    <string name="about_developer_title">Developer</string>
    <string name="about_legal_title">Legal</string>

    <string name="about_wsjf_text">WSJF (Weighted Shortest Job First) is a prioritization technique recommended by Dean Leffingwell that determines job sequencing, calculated as the cost of delay divided by job duration. Jobs that can deliver the most value (or cost of delay), and are of the shortest duration are selected first for implementation.</string>
    <string name="about_cod_text">There are three primary elements that contribute to the cost of delay:\n \nUser Value: What is the relative value of the feature in the eyes of the business or the user?\n\nTime Value: Describes the need of delivering something in a timescale.\n\nRROE Value: Gives a relative value for the need of a business to eliminate risks earlier or the potential for new business opportunity to be derived from the task.\n\nAlgorithm: Cost of Delay = (User Value + Time Value + RROE Value)"</string>
    <string name="about_job_duration_text">To determine the job duration, a job size proxy is used.\n\nJob Size: The estimate of length of time to implement the feature.</string>
    <string name="about_result_text">Finally, when all the aforementioned values have been established, we have a reasonable straightforward calculation for comparing tasks via WSJF. \n\nWSJF = (User Value + Time Value + RROE Value) / Job Size</string>
    <string name="about_developer_text">Alexandros Parpas\n\nSend Feedback</string>
    <string name="about_legal_material_icons">Copyright 2016 Material Design icons by Google\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="about_legal_app_icon">Copyright 2014 Android Asset Studio\n\nLicensed under a Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Unported License.; You must give appropriate credit, provide a link to the license, and indicate if changes were made. You may do so in any reasonable manner, but not in any way that suggests the licensor endorses you or your use. You may obtain a copy of the license in:\n\nhttps://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0</string>

    <string name="date_picker_title">Start Date</string>
    <string name="no_data_available">There are no tasks. You can add a task by clicking on the + button below. </string>

    <string name="info_user_value">What is the relative value of the feature in the eyes of the business or the user? (1 being the lowest value and 10 being the highest)?\n\nAnswers the following questions:\n&#8226; Do our users prefer this over that?\n&#8226; What is the revenue impact on our business?\n&#8226; Is there a potential penalty or other negative impact if we delay?</string>
    <string name="info_time_value">This value describes the need of delivering something in a timescale. (1 being a low "need" and 10 being highest "need")\n\nAnswers the following questions:\n&#8226; How does the user/business value decay over time?\n&#8226; Is there a fixed deadline?\n&#8226; Will they wait for us or move to another solution?\n&#8226; What is current effect on customer satisfaction?\n\n</string>
    <string name="info_rroe_value">Gives a relative value for the need of a business to eliminate risks earlier or the potential for new business opportunity to be derived from the task. (1 being a low "need" and 10 being highest "need")\n\nAnswers the following questions:\n&#8226; What else does this do for our business?\n&#8226; Does it reduce the risk of this or future delivery?\n&#8226; Is there value in the information we will receive?\n&#8226; Will this feature enable new business opportunities?</string>
    <string name="info_job_size_value">The estimate of length of time to implement the feature. (1 being the shortest duration and 10 being the highest)</string>

    <string name="tasks_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3946646782063719/1378706385</string>
    <string name="details_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3946646782063719/3053915989</string>
    <string name="app_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3946646782063719~7282625982</string>


</resources>
